[{"answer": "We're not? Of course we are not! Then if we are not Goa'ulds, who are we", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, Yes! That's right, I am my friend from the planet that place, pleased to meet you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes, Yes! That's right, I am my friend from the planet that place, pleased to meet you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, I'm my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No, I'm my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, inventions to fight the Goa'uld", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I realize what I look like, but I'm telling you that machine somehow switched us", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ask me anything, something only my friend would know", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Isn't that what you are doing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Then you must be strange as well", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Then you must be strange as well", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I am called Ma'chello", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Indeed we ar", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "A credit card, where would I find such a card", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "But I do not wish to fight any longer. From now on I only want to eat hamburgers and French fries and ice cream sundaes and I want to be with good people like you, my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, no my friend, only evil things must come to an end. For good things such as ourselves, it is possible to go on forever", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I am not joking", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It is presently my head, my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It is presently my head, my friend", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "And if it is not", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "The Goa'uld use host because they think they are better than humans, because they believe they deserve it. You're a Goa'uld Ma'chello. I am nothing but a host to you", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "My wife is still alive, there is a chance I could still save her, you are stealing that chance", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Holiday.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 24}]